{\clip(190,219,190,219)\t(0,600,\clip(100,217,280,220))\t(16600,17100,\clip(190,217,190,220))}m 0 0 m 180 1 l 0 1 l 0 0 l 180 0
{\clip(80,220,300,220)\t(0,600,\clip(80,197,300,240))\t(3700,4200,\clip(80,220,300,220))}翻\h译
xiaoshu0430\h\h\h爱笑的海豚\h\h\h\hOrun!que
ZoeyJolly\h\h\h西卡卡卡\h\h\h\h马丁马丁回音山
{\clip(80,220,300,220)\t(0,600,\clip(80,197,300,240))\t(3700,4200,\clip(80,220,300,220))}校对\h&\h后期
粲呀粲\h\h\h\h你以为列
{\clip(80,220,300,220)\t(0,600,\clip(80,197,300,240))\t(3700,4200,\clip(80,220,300,220))}总监
大红
片头推广合作洽谈\h请联系普罗米修斯邮箱\hPLMXS2016@GmaiL.com
看着无辜的人死去
伦敦
英国\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h伦敦
公寓的主人在周三深夜发现了他们
The owner of the flat discovered them late Wednesday night.
是他
It's him.
是的
Yeah.
公寓的主人在周三深夜发现了他们
The owner of the flat discovered them late Wednesday night.
明信片杀戮
快点  火车要开了
Come on, it's gonna go.
-这张真的很棒  -西尔维娅
- It's a really good one. - Sylvia!
这里好吵
So loud in there.
这儿有人吗
Are these free?
坐吧
They're all yours.
火车上的足球迷真的烦死人了
Football fans on trains are the worst.
-是的  -我是皮耶特
- Yeah. - I'm Pieter.
我是麦克
I'm Mac.
这位是西尔维娅
And this is Sylvia.
预算很紧  是吧
On a tight budget, huh?
做剪贴簿呢
Scrapbook.
文身不错啊  朋友
Nice tats, man.
多谢
Thanks.
我差点两个胳膊都纹了
I'm almost done with both sleeves.
就像一幅活画布
Like a living canvas.
太美了
They're beautiful.
我老婆挺会欣赏艺术的
My wife appreciates art.
天哪  谢谢你
Oh, jesus! Thank you.
起来
Get up.
我一直在试着给你打电话
I've been trying to call you.
我想见金伯利
I want to see Kimberly.
现在几点了
Hey, what time is it?
九点了  你看起来糟透了
9:00. You look like shit.
靠
Oh, fuck.
我感觉也糟透了
Oh, I feel like shit.
准备一下  我给你叫点吃的
Get ready, I'll order you something to eat.
好的  天哪  我不饿  停下来
Oh, okay. God damn it, I'm not hungry. Stop.
好吧  你啥也别想吃了
Fine. I won't get you anything to eat.
靠  瓦莱丽
Fuck. Valerie.
起开  不行
Get off! No!
没什么用
It doesn't help.
我要见她
I need to see her.
你不该见她
You shouldn't.
好吗  相信我
Okay? Just trust me.
那我要看看事发地点
Then I want to see where it happened.
让我缓缓
Give me a minute.
这样很不符合规定
This is highly unconventional.
我他妈不在乎
I don't give a damn.
我要看
I want to see it.
把带子剪了
Just cut the tape.
这里仍然是犯罪现场
It is still a crime scene.
我当警察也三十年了
Yeah. I've been a cop for 30 years.
我知道在犯罪现场该怎么走
I know how to walk through a crime scene.
好吧
Okay.
恐怕你得在楼下等着
I'm afraid you'll have to wait downstairs.
我们已经采集了指纹  但是
We have dusted for prints, but...
这里已经有好几百人租过了
It's been rented by hundreds of people.
你问过大楼里的每个人了吗
You've questioned everyone in these buildings?
是的
Yes.
没有人看到或听到任何东西
No one saw or heard anything.
水槽里有两个玻璃杯
There were two glasses in the sink,
只有受害者的指纹
only the victims' prints.
没人看到什么  也没人听到什么
No one saw anything, no one heard anything,
也没有强行进入的痕迹
and there was no forced entry...
我女儿认识那个凶手
My daughter knew the killer.
她是警察的孩子
She's a cop's kid
她是不会让陌生人进来的
she would never let some stranger in.
我们需要查一下他们的信用卡
We need to check their credit cards,
社交软件  全要查一遍  找出他们去过哪里
social media, everything. Find out where they were.
都在办了
It's all in motion.
血迹在哪里
Where's the blood?
他们的血都流干了
Their blood was completely drained.
受害者当时躺在床上
The victims were on the bed.
男性受害者的眼睛被针撑开
The male victim's eyes were held open with pins.
他的嘴唇被钉上了什么东西
His lips had something attached to them.
女性受害者在他的怀里
The female victim was in his arms.
胳膊从肘部以下被切断
The arms were severed below the elbow.
左上臂被插入男性受害者的嘴里
The left upper arm was inserted into the male victim's mouth.
你觉得他为什么要给他们摆这些姿势
Why do you think he posed them?
我想是因为他极度变态
Because he's extremely sick, I'd imagine.
但他是想表达些什么
But he was saying something.
布置这样一个精心设计的犯罪现场
A highly organised crime scene like this
一定有什么特别的原因
is done for a specific reason.
和在马德里被谋杀的那对夫妇
The couple that was murdered in Madrid,
有相似之处吗
are there similarities?
有一些
A few.
它们有联系吗  督察
Were they staged, Inspector?
我说不好
I can't say.
目前还不清楚
At this stage, it's not clear
这些是不是孤立的事件
whether or not these are isolated incidents.
我们都知道这不是随机杀人的作案手法
We both know this is not the MO of a random killer.
美国是个傲慢的国家
America's an arrogant country.
但愿没有冒犯到你
I hope I don't offend you.
没事
No.
你要去哪儿  朋友
Where are you headed actually, man?
往北走
Working my way north.
你呢
You?
差不多  没什么计划
Same. No real plans.
我们可以在一起玩
We should all hang out together.
选个地方下车
Pick a place to get off.
来嘛  会很有意思的
Come on, it'll be fun.
探索一下新世界
Venture into the unknown.
我们喝点小酒再谈
Let's get some drinks and then we can discuss it.
伏特加怎么样
Vodka?
还有什么
What else?
我真不敢相信你差点叫他和我们一起去了
I can't believe you almost invited him to come with us.
我没过脑子  好吗  对不起
I just didn't think, okay? I'm sorry.
我当然想每一刻都和你腻在一起
Like obviously, I'd much rather spend every second with you.
只和你
You only.
我只是觉得他有点奇怪
I just thought he was a bit strange,
你不觉得吗   兰道夫先生
didn't you, Mr Randolph?
你猜怎么着  我真这么觉得
You know what? I did,
兰道夫夫人
Mrs Randolph.
你记不记得她八岁的时候
You remember when she was eight...
在空手道课上
Karate class?
她可喜欢那门课了
She loved that class.
你是说她可喜欢让你以她为荣了
You mean she loved making you proud.
你就不能让他们去夏威夷
You couldn't just let them go to Hawaii
或者去加勒比海度蜜月吗
or the Caribbean for their honeymoon?
不行
No...
你得当那个好人啊
You had to be the hero,
给她的欧洲大冒险买单
buy her the big Euro adventure.
这就是我们过不下去的原因之一
That's one of the reasons it didn't work out,
她最爱的只能是你
you always had to be the one she loved the most.
你为什么要把她送到这里来
Why did you have to send her here?
为什么
Why?
你为什么要把她送到这里来
Why did you have to send her here?
为什么  为什么
Why? Why!
我就是  我感觉我要疯了
I just... I feel like I'm going crazy.
真的对不起
I'm so sorry.
这事儿怎么就发生在我们身上了
How did this happen to us?
一瓶伏特加  三个杯子
One bottle of vodka, and three cups...
看来只用得上一个杯子了
I guess one cup then.
我
I...
我感觉我在抛弃她
I feel like I'm abandoning her.
不  你没有
No. You're not.
我在这儿呢  好吗
I'm here, okay?
我就是干这个的
This is what I do.
你
You'll...
不管是什么  你都会告诉我的  对吧
You'll let me know everything, right, no matter what?
当然了
Of course I will.
不  你不会的
No, you won't.
我什么都听见了  雅各布
I heard everything, Jacob.
有人残害了我们的女儿
Someone mutilated our daughter.
找到他
Find him.
您要去往哪里
起点
伦敦
终点
马德里市
出发时间
立刻
查找路线
伦敦(英国)
马德里市(西班牙)
4次换乘
12.25小时
在一对年轻的美国夫妇
Over two weeks after the gruesome murder
惨遭谋杀两周后
of a young American couple,
伦敦警察厅拒绝证实有关报道
the Metropolitan Police are refusing to confirm reports
报道称  记者查尔斯·哈德威克
that a journalist, Charles Hardwick,
在案发前几天收到一张明信片
received a postcard with information
上面写有关于凶杀的信息
on the killings days before...
先生
Sir.
别碰我
Get your hands off me.
给我半个小时  我再给你回电  谢谢
Give me half an hour, I'll... I'll call you back, thanks.
给卡农先生倒杯咖啡  好吗
Would you get Mr Kanon a coffee?
不好意思
Sorry about that.
我相信他只是想努力做好他的工作
I'm sure he's just trying to do his job.
是的
Yeah.
我们都在努力  请坐吧
Well, we're all trying to do that. Why don't you take a seat?
距我女儿被杀已经两个多星期了
It's been over two goddamn weeks since my daughter's murder.
你一直在躲我
You've been avoiding me,
而且我知道  你有新线索了
and I know that you have new leads.
没错  我们确实有
Absolutely, we do,
但是我不能和公众透露任何东西
but nothing I can share with a member of the public,
不管他们和这个案件有多大关系
however close they are to the case.
警察同事呢  可以吗
How about a fellow cop?
我在新闻上听说了那张明信片
This postcard that I hear about on the news,
本应该由你来告诉我的  写了什么
when I should be hearing from you... What does it say?
你知道我不能告诉你的
You know I can't tell you that.
就这吗  你就只跟我说这些吗
Is that it? Is that what you're gonna tell me?
没别的可说了
That's everything.
好吧
Okay.
我心头需要被解答的疑问
The questions that I have that need to be answered?
我会自己找到答案
I will find the answers myself.
我不建议你这么做
I don't recommend you do that.
我给过你机会了
You had your chance.
《卫报》  《观察家报》
负三层  门要开了
floor minus three. Doors open.
马丁
哈德威克
你好  有什么事儿吗
Hi, can I help you?
我其实在等他
I'm waiting for him actually.
-找我吗  -查尔斯·哈德威克是吧
- Me? - Charles Hardwick?
你收到过一张明信片  对吗
You received a postcard, right?
你在私人领地
You're on private property.
我女儿死了
My daughter is dead.
你收到了杀她的人寄来的明信片
And you received a postcard from the person that killed her.
我无权谈论这件事
I'm not at liberty to talk about this.
先生  我只想知道
Look, sir, all I wanna know is
在马德里有没有人收到了这样的明信片
if anyone in Madrid received a postcard?
你有孩子吗
Do you have kids?
没关系  我没事
It's okay, I'm good.
我被告知  我和别人讨论这件事是违法的
I've been told that it's breaking the law if I discuss the details.
你有几个孩子
How many kids do you have?
一个  有个小闺女
One... Baby girl.
对一个父亲来说  没什么比女儿更特别了
There is nothing more special to a father than a daughter.
一名西班牙记者
A Spanish reporter
收到一张普拉多的明信片
got a postcard of the Prado.
很明显
The victims,
受害者的嘴唇
apparently, they had their lips...
被切断了
Severed.
对不起  那是我们最后一班飞机了
I'm sorry, that was our last flight.
我们明天早上6点有一班
We have one leaving tomorrow at 6:00 A.M.
是的  你已经告诉我很多次了
Yup, you have told me this now numerous times.
你给我听好  这是警方的事
Listen to me. This is a police matter.
紧急事件  你必须让我上飞机
An emergency. You have to get me on a plane.
先生  我和您说过那是最后一班飞机了
Sir, please, I've told you that was our last flight.
知道  但帮助顾客是你的工作  对吧
I know. It's your job to be helpful, right?
帮我
Be helpful.
帮我个忙  用你的电脑
Do me a favour, and get on your computer
帮我找一班转机的航班
and find me a connecting flight.
我不介意在哪转机
I don't even care where it connects from,
我就是等不到明天了  我现在就得走
I just can't have it be tomorrow. I need it to be now.
所有的航班都满员了  很抱歉
All other flights are full. I'm sorry.
我必须要去马德里
I need to get to Madrid.
我说的哪句你没明白
What part of that do you not understand?
先生  你冷静一点
Sir, you need to calm down.
我很冷静  就没有人能给我安排个航班吗
I am calm! Can someone just get me a fucking flight?
一切都好吗  女士
Is everything okay, madam?
真好
Perfect.
先生  你得和我们走一趟了
Sir, you need to come with us.
好吧
Yeah.
谢谢你的帮助
Thank you for your help.
您好  可以看下您的护照吗
Hi there. Can I see your passport?
好
Yup.
你这是在自我折磨  警探
Torturing yourself, Detective.
我知道这有多难
I do understand how hard this is.
真的吗
Really?
你真知道吗
Do you?
我觉得你根本不知道这有多难
See, I don't think you have any idea how hard this is.
回家吧  请节哀  先生
Go home and mourn, sir.
"回家吧"
"Go home"?
不把我女儿带回来  我哪儿都不去
I'm not going anywhere without my little girl.
我很同情你  卡农先生  我向你保证
I am sympathetic, Mr Kanon, I assure you...
"卡农警探"
"Detective Kanon".
叫我卡农警探
It's Detective Kanon.
我最不想要的就是你的同情
And the last thing I want is your sympathy.
这些是你女儿的私人物品
Your daughter's personal belongings.
请好好想想我跟你说的话吧
Now please, think about what I said.
报道称  这对夫妇当时正在欧洲背包旅行
Reports suggest the couple were backpacking through Europe.
他们在慕尼黑的大教堂青年旅馆
They had been staying at the Cathedral youth hostel
住了将近一周的时间
in Munich for a week.
据推测  这或许是这一系列
Early speculation indicates that this is the third
残忍凶杀案的第三起
in a series of brutal murders.
德国\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h慕尼黑
进来吧
他今天又给吓着了
我就该救一条德国的狗  而不是叙利亚的
你这是做了件善事
遛完后好好喂喂他
卡农警探
Detective Kanon.
慕尼黑有家餐厅
There's still a restaurant in Munich
在里面又能喝咖啡又能抽烟
where you can drink a cup of coffee and smoke a cigarette.
看来这两样你都需要
You look like you could use both.
这段时间肯定很难熬
This must be a very painful time.
你们找到她的手了吗
Did you find her hands?
没有
No.
但是有
But there were...
但是有不属于她的肢体部位
There were body parts that didn't belong?
让我猜一下
Let me guess,
案发现场并没有发现酒瓶子
there were no liquor bottles at the scene,
但是受害者
but the victims,
身体里检测出大量酒精
they had high levels of alcohol in their system.
他们或许被下药了
They were probably drugged.
我们发现了环喷托酯的痕迹
We found traces of cyclopentolate.
睫状肌麻痹剂
是一种滴眼药
It's an agent in eye drops.
他们  他们是一对年轻的夫妇吗
And they were a young... A young, married couple?
疯子总是痴迷于青春与美貌
Crazy people often obsess about youth and beauty.
但不是所有疯子都会残害受害者
But they don't all mutilate their victims.
这个混蛋  他在很有目标地挑选受害者
This bastard, he's very selective about his targets.
确实他的举动
Certainly his actions
和现有的一些案例不符
don't fit with existing profiles.
明信片  还有照片
The postcard, then the photograph.
什么照片
What photograph?
我也希望我可以告诉你
I wish I could tell you.
是说有我女儿的照片吗
Is there a photograph of my daughter?
是的
Yes.
她还活着吗
Is she alive?
我需要看看
I need to see it.
已经被列为证据了
It's already been marked as evidence.
属于伦敦政府调查的一部分了
It's part of the London investigation.
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
这些眼睛  不属于受害者
The eyes. They don't belong to the victims.
上帝啊
Jesus!
卡农警探  我得去问案了
Detective Kanon, now I have someone to question.
你们是在浪费时间
You're wasting your time.
他已经不在这里了
He's moved on.
瑞典\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h斯德哥尔摩
爱情不朽
黛西·隆巴德
隆巴德女士
Ms Lombard,
现在有一起正在调查的案件需要你的配合
you are now part of an ongoing investigation.
泄露明信片上的内容是违法的
It is a criminal offense to reveal what is on the postcard.
你明白吗
Understand?
从明天开始  每天早上和下午
Each day your mail will be opened
你的个人信件  警察会先打开看一下
by a police officer, morning and afternoon, starting tomorrow.
-可以吧  -可以
- Okay? - Okay.
警方证实
Police sources have confirmed
一名住在斯德哥尔摩的美国记者
that an American journalist living in Stockholm,
今早收到了一张明信片
received a postcard this morning.
晚安  隆巴德女士
Good night, Ms Lombard.
晚安
Night.
隆巴德女士
Ms Lombard.
什么事  你要干嘛
What? What do you want?
我是卡农警探
My name is Detective Kanon,
我只是想问问你明信片的事情
and I just want to ask you about the postcard.
如果你是个警探  就去找那些警探去
If you're a detective, talk to the detectives.
求你了  他们还会给你寄一些别的东西
Please, they're gonna send you something else,
到那时  他们就已经死了
and by then, they'll be dead!
求你了  我只是想帮忙
Please, I just want to help.
我把我的名片留给你了
I'm leaving you my card.
看来是命中注定  我们遇见他两次了
Well, maybe it's fate, running into him twice.
他看见我们了  我们也没别的选择了
Well, he's seen us now. So, we don't have much choice.
老兄  这么巧又遇到你了
Hey, man. How bizarre bumping into you!
你们本来以为甩掉我了
And you thought you'd ditched me.
不是啊  我们在最后一刻下车了
No, God, we just... We got off the train last minute.
你那会儿在吧台  我们留了便条的
You were at the bar. So... We left a note.
没有便条
No note.
麦克  我以为你
Mac, I assumed that you...
不啊  我以为是你
No, I left it to you.
你们美国人可真够逗的
You Americans crack me up.
来喝一杯吧  生命在于享受
Come, let's go for drink, life's for the living.
老兄  你在这儿待多久了
So, er, how long have you been here for, man?
好几天了
A couple of days.
我们也是  你住哪儿
Yeah? Us too. Where are you staying?
大广场边上
By the, er... Stortorget.
你们呢
You?
就在这地方后面
Oh... Just a place back there.
六点酒店  挺好的
The Six, fancy.
你是怎么知道的
How do you know that?
我在跟踪你们
I'm stalking you.
这个袋子啊
Ah, the bag.
六点酒店
伦敦
马德里
斯德哥尔摩
第一起与第二起谋杀案相隔8天
The first murders were eight days apart.
慕尼黑案正好在伦敦案后16天发生
Munich was exactly 16 days after London.
这可能是一种作案模式
It could be a pattern.
这意味着还有未被发现的受害者
Which means there are undiscovered victims out there.
我们正在与联合特别小组密切合作
We're working closely with the joint task force.
这是一次全欧洲范围的查案
This is a Europe-wide investigation.
你很清楚这就能解释为什么
You do understand that this would explain
我女儿的双手还是没有找到
why my daughter's hands are still missing.
卡农警探
Detective Kanon...
你听到我刚才说的了吧
Did you hear what I just said?
我们已经向各处下发了凶手侧写
All our units have been provided with the profile.
你们的侧写是错的
Your profile is wrong.
听着  这个凶手的谋杀手法非常具体
Look, this killer's brand of murder is very specific,
很难进行准确的侧写
extremely hard to profile.
像他这样的人可以很有魅力  有活力
People like him can be charming, dynamic.
我处理过这样的案件
I have worked cases that are...
我知道你是个能力很强的警探
I'm sure you are a hotshot detective,
但我们行事不像美国警方
but we don't conduct ourselves like the American police.
你说这话什么意思
What the fuck does that mean?
你们是先开枪  再问问题
Shoot first, ask questions later.
我才不在乎你们想的是什么
I don't give a rat's ass what either of you think.
你们有四天的时间可以阻止一场凶杀案
You've got exactly four days to prevent a murder.
我对你没有意见  我也很同情你
It's not personal. I do sympathise, of course,
但是你的客观性
but your objectivity has...
妈的
Fuck!
年轻夫妇在马德里遇害
美国新婚夫妇在伦敦被残忍杀害
托马斯和金伯利·斯蒂文森
纽约市警察局
雅各布·卡农  纽约市警察局
警探
蒂尔达  我想做一篇关于谋杀案的报道
Tilda, I have a human interest piece on the killings.
-不行  -请听我说完
- No. - Wait, please.
我
I...
我在芝加哥一名记者手下实习的时候
The reporter I interned for in Chicago,
他写过类似的报道
he did a similar piece
那年那篇报道的销量稳居第一
and it out-sold everything that year.
路还好找吗
So, you found it okay?
还好
yeah.
有肯帮忙的人  谢天谢地
People are helpful and thank God
他们能说一点英语
they speak a little bit of English.
你昨晚为什么没跟我说你女儿的事情
Why didn't you tell me about your daughter last night?
因为太难了
Because it's hard.
我很难张口谈论这件事
It's not something I want to open with.
你想从我这得到什么
What do you want from me?
我想知道明信片上面写了什么
I want to know what was on the postcard.
那你想从我这里得到什么
What do you want from me?
我被卷进了这个破事
I've been thrown into this mess,
没有人告诉我实情
and nobody is telling me anything.
我每周都在报纸上写一篇文章
Look, I write a weekly piece at a newspaper
讲述我这个美国人在陌生国家的生活
about being an American living in a strange country.
为什么这样的破事
Why would something like this
会发生在我的身上
happen to someone like me?
抱歉  我明白不知道内情有多难受
I'm sorry, I know it's hard being on the outside.
我也是同样的心情  我想要帮忙
And I feel like that too, and... And I want to help.
我联系了那个西班牙的记者
So, I, erm... I contacted this Spanish journalist
还有那个《卫报》的哈德威克
and that guy Hardwick from The Guardian.
但是吧  也没有太大收获
But you know, it doesn't make much sense.
好像我们这些做记者的
I mean, there seems to be no connection
彼此之前关联性不大
between what we do as journalists.
有专门写政治的
You know, one covers politics,
有写财经的  有写文娱的
one covers finance, one culture.
明信片上写什么了
And the postcards?
我们来看一下
Well, what do we have?
马德里那张写的是
In Madrid, it said,
"至死不渝"
"Till death do us part."
伦敦那张写的是  "看着无辜的人死去"
In London, "Watch the innocent die,"
慕尼黑那张写的是  "真相往往使人痛苦"
in Munich it said, "Feel the pain, see the truth."
这张写的是  "爱情不朽"
And here, "Love will never die."
每一句话后面都有省略号
And every sentence is always followed by an ellipsis.
"点  点  点"
"Dot, dot, dot".
-意味着待续  -是的
- A continuation. - Yeah.
他用明信片来宣告  他来到了这个城市
He announces his arrival in a city with the postcard.
选择一对夫妇
Selects a couple...
年轻  新婚  幸福
Young, newly married, happy...
你喜欢吃鲱鱼吗
You like herring?
这是我做过的最糟糕的决定
It's the worst decision I've ever made.
我本来不想说实话
I was trying to be polite.
他说她为什么要分开行动来着
Why did he say she wasn't with him?
他们都是很有个性的人
They're very independent people.
她喜欢坐飞机  他喜欢坐火车
She likes to fly, and he likes trains.
他来了
Here he comes.
麦克  西尔维娅
Mac, Sylvia,
这是我老婆  也是我的纹身师  奈安姬
meet my wife and the artist behind my tattoos, Nienke.
很高兴见到你们俩
It's a pleasure meeting you both.
他都没提起过你
He kept your existence very quiet.
为我老公说句话
Well, in my husband's defence,
似乎他还没来得及和你俩说
it sounds as if you two ditched him
你们就先把他甩掉了
before he could reveal very much.
无力反驳
Touche.
你们想再喝点什么吗
Would you like another drink?
来点更猛的酒呗
Maybe something stronger?
可以啊
Yes, we would.
好啊
Yeah.
必须的
Absolutely.
-那走吧  -要龙舌兰
- Okay, let's go. - Tequila!
你们有去过比约克斯卡吗
Have you guys been to Bjorkskar yet?
-是那个岛吗  -是
- Is that the island? - Yes.
群岛的一部分
Part of the archipelago.
斯德哥尔摩被称为群岛之城
每年的这个时候  风景绝了
This time of year, it's really something.
又荒凉又有情调
Desolate, moody.
坐船很快就到了  你们可以去看看
It's just a short ferry ride. You should come.
死亡
爱情
痛苦
斯德哥尔摩明信片
爱情不朽
爱情
我知道  把手指插到伤口里的场景
The finger in the wound I recognise,
但如果是女人的手
but the woman's hand...
就不知道了
No.
《圣·托马斯的怀疑》
The Incredulity of Saint Thomas.
许多艺术家都描绘过这个场面
It has been depicted by many artists.
这幅是画家卡拉瓦乔的作品
This is by Caravaggio.
使徒托马斯
Thomas the Apostle,
怀疑耶稣是否真的复活
skeptical of Jesus' resurrection.
你看这里
You see here,
他用手指试探  看伤口是否流血
he is testing the wound to see if it bleeds.
"除非我看到他手心里的钉痕"
"Unless I see the nail marks in his hands"
"并用手插入他的侧肋"
"and put my hand into his side,"
"否则我是不会相信的"
"I will not believe it."
"怀疑的托马斯"这个词就是这么来的
Hence the phrase, "Doubting Thomas."
《农神吞噬其子》
Saturn Devouring His Son,
是弗朗西斯科·戈雅的画作  展出于伦敦
by Francisco Goya, exhibited in London.
明信片上说
Postcard said,
"看着无辜的人死去"
"Watch the innocent die."
这幅是《圣·托马斯的怀疑》
This, The Incredulity of St Thomas,
《圣·托马斯的怀疑》
卡拉瓦乔
绘于1601-1602年
就是在这栋楼里展出的
on display, right there in that building.
你怎么不把这些信息告诉
Why didn't you bring this
斯德哥尔摩特别小组呢
to the Stockholm task force?
因为他们只会循规蹈矩
Because they're by the book,
而你看起来
and you seem...
似乎更能接受各种可能性
You seem open to possibilities.
等等  暂停
Whoa, stop.
我见过这个人
I've seen him before.
这个女人是跟他一起行动的
This woman is moving off with him.
不是"他"
That's not a "him."
而是"他们"
It's a "them."
退回去  到前面一天
Go back, to the day before.
停  他们来了
Stop. There they are.
快啊
Come on.
快给我把头抬起来
Pick up your goddamn head!
好了大家都过来一下
确认当前案件不再是单人作案
我们要联系国际刑警组织和移民局
所有年龄在二十到四十岁之间的夫妇
火车站  机场
旅馆  招待所  出租屋
布网所有博物馆  查找过去四天内的所有监控录像
好吗
很好  行动吧
四十多个摄像头  竟没一个拍到他们的脸
Forty-odd cameras and not one of them picked up their faces!
说真的  你要放松点
Seriously, you must take it easy on yourself.
你推进了调查  这是件好事
You've gotten us somewhere, and that's a good thing.
霍格伦德警探答应我了
Detective Hoglund promised me
之后所有情报她都会告知你
she will include you in all intelligence going forward.
真他娘的好
Big fucking deal.
明天这个时候  另一对夫妇会死
Tomorrow, at this time, another couple will be dead.
把他们的护照都交叉对比一下
Look, have them cross-reference passports.
任何到过马德里  伦敦
Any couples that have been to Madrid, London,
斯德哥尔摩  还有这里的夫妇
Stockholm, here,
找到他们真的没有那么难
it can't be that hard to find them.
欧盟要执行一项行动自由协议
The European Union operates a freedom of movement agreement.
过境还是有很多漏洞可钻的
We still have porous borders.
你是在告诉我  这里连最笨的那种
Are you telling me there's no fool-proof way
登记人们边境往来的系统  也没有了吗
of registering people's comings and goings?
由于恐怖主义和难民危机
With terrorism and the refugee crisis,
一些国家是恢复了临时管制
some countries have reinstated temporary controls.
但总的来说  没有
But generally speaking, no.
你得想办法让我翻阅所有文件
You have to let me see all the files.
你是想让我现在就退休吗
You want me to retire immediately, huh?
不  我没这样想
No, I don't.
我只是想帮你抓住他们
I want to help you catch them.
这两人可能有嫌疑
男方7天前来到斯德哥尔摩
女方几天后也来了
查过他们的信用卡记录了吗
还没有
现在就去
西尔维娅
Sylvia?
你是不是丢了什么东西
Did you lose a little thing?
那是我的帽子  你从哪儿弄来的
That's my hat. Where did you get it?
这就是你给我留的"便条"
It's your so-called note.
给我吧
Give it to me.
好啊
Yeah.
你个怪胎
You weirdo.
这样吧  就当作礼物送你了
You know what? A gift.
那你就别想拿回去了
You're not gonna get it back though.
我会把它好好留着的
Going to keep it.
一个二十六岁  一个二十三岁
Twenty-six, and twenty-three.
都是荷兰人
They're Dutch.
根据他的护照信息
He gave his passport information
他在金斯图加坦租了一套公寓
to rent an apartment on Kindstugatan.
据房主说
According to the owner,
他们是从德国来的  一前一后到这里
they arrived separately from Germany.
我们有证据能证明  在机场
At the airport, we have evidence
女方把英镑兑成了瑞典克朗
she changed sterling into Swedish krona.
而男方有两项非法持有毒品的犯罪记录
He has two recorded offences for drug possession.
女方在纹身店工作
She works at a tattoo parlour,
在里特维尔德学院待了两年
and has spent two years at the Gerrit Rietveld Academie.
那是什么地方
What's that?
是一所艺术学校
It's an art school.
欢迎
Welcome.
我们有正事要办了
We got jobs to do.
房主说他们今天一整天都不在这儿
The owner says they haven't been here all day.
这顶帽子
This hat...
是金伯利的
It's Kimberly's.
卡农警探  我很遗憾
Detective Kanon, I'm so sorry.
耳朵
The ears...
是慕尼黑案里的
They're from the Munich murders.
对  你很可能是对的
Yeah, you may be right.
在其他地方  一定还有未被发现的受害者
Somewhere, there are undiscovered victims.
我是安东尼奥·卡诺瓦
This is Antonio Canova,
《丘比特吻醒赛姬》
Psyche Revived by Cupid's Kiss.
我猜  展出在
Let me guess, exhibited at...
就在这里  斯德哥尔摩国家博物馆
Here in the National museum in Stockholm.
它代表丘比特用吻  唤醒了赛姬的尸体
And it represents Cupid waking Psyche's lifeless corpse,
而阴阳两隔的恋人得以重聚
and reuniting the torn apart lovers.
"爱情不朽"
"Love will never die."
那你觉得耳朵
So do you think that the ears
是用来代表翅膀的吗
are supposed to represent the wings?
我想是的
I guess so.
我还觉得
I also think that...
马德里案那句话也代表了一个雕塑
Madrid is a sculpture.
这个  是罗丹的《吻》
This one, Rodin's The Kiss.
你看嘴唇部分
I mean, look at the lips.
他们没有碰触到一起  就像被隔开了一样
They don't actually touch, like they were interrupted...
"至死不渝"
"Till death do us part."
对
Yeah.
明信片上写的
Messages on the postcards...
死亡  痛苦  我
Death, pain, I...
我能懂  但是
I get it, but...
但爱情呢  我只是
But love? I just...
不明白他们想表达什么意思
I don't understand what they're trying to say.
可能  爱情是致命的
Er, that love is deadly,
爱情是痛苦的
that love is painful?
我
I...
我觉得他们是想毁掉欢愉
I think they're trying to destroy joy.
我  抱歉  我
I'm... I'm sorry. I...
我刚刚一下子给忘了
I forgot for a moment.
没事的
It's okay.
我只想带我女儿回家
I just want to bring her home.
美国\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h纽约
我刚刚睡着了  天知道怎么回事  我感觉
I fell asleep, God knows how. I feel like...
我已经好几周没睡觉了
I haven't slept in weeks.
我穿上衣服  去办公室
I get dressed and go to the office,
只是为了避免
just so that I don't
整天坐在家里  嫌弃自己帮不上忙
sit at home feeling useless.
我觉得  "帮不上忙"
I think that "useless" is
正是我们该有的感觉
exactly how we're supposed to feel.
我得挂电话了  我会随时告诉你进展的
Hey, I got to go. I will keep you posted.
我保证  好吗
I promise, okay?
看  这是一家店监控器的画面
Okay, see, this is footage from a storefront security camera,
离渡轮码头只有一个街区
one block away from the ferry terminal.
我们慢放视频  增强画面
So, we slowed it down and had it enhanced.
你拿了钥匙吗
Have you got the keys?
没有  钥匙在你那里
No, you have the keys.
我拿了钥匙
I have a key.
你好  我们要退房  418房间
Erm, hi, we are checking out of room 418.
请稍等账单出账
Let me get your bill ready.
兰道夫先生和夫人是吗
Mr and Mrs Randolph.
是的
Mmm-hmm.
"兰道夫先生和夫人"
"Mr and Mrs Randolph."
我就喜欢听这句话
I love the sound of that.
警察  警察
Police! Police!
怎么回事
What is going on?
能告诉我们发生了什么吗
Can you tell us what's happening?
请问  有人能告诉我怎么回事吗
Can somebody please tell me what's going on?
你知道  他们俩是谁吗
Can you tell us who they are?
知道  来自阿姆斯特丹的皮耶特和奈安姬
Yeah, that's Pieter and Nienke, from Amsterdam.
等等  为什么  他们做了什么吗
Wait, why? Did they do something?
难道这就是你带我们来这里的原因吗
Is that why you brought us here?
操  我的天呐
Fuck! Jesus Christ!
你们和他们一起乘渡船去了比约克斯卡
You took a ferry with them to Bjorkskar.
就在那儿发生的吗
That happened there?
你当时和他们在一起吗
You were with them?
我们在监控录像上看到了你
We have you on surveillance footage.
是  我们当时是和他们在一起
Yeah. Yeah, we were with them.
我们  我们乘了渡船
We... We took a ferry,
我们计划去探险  然后留在那儿过夜
we planned to explore and stay over.
但后来麦克感觉身体不舒服  我们就走了
But then Mac wasn't feeling well, so we left.
所以你们乘下一班渡轮走了
So you left on the next ferry?
在国外  身体不舒服不大一样
There's something about being sick in a foreign country,
感觉更糟糕
you know, it's like, double worse.
你只想快点回家  躺在自己的床上
You just want to be at home in your own bed,
叫餐  吃点东西
eating room service.
我们回到酒店
We went back to the hotel.
我点了鸡汤  几乎没怎么喝
I had chicken soup and I barely touched it,
西尔维娅点了汉堡和薯条
and Sylvia had burger and fries.
是的  我们乘渡轮回来了  我还有收据
Yeah, we got the ferry back. I have a receipt.
麦克还总是笑我
Mac always makes fun of me
因为我把这些都收集到我的收集册里
because I save everything for a memory book.
我可以拿给你们看  就在我的行李里
I can show you. It's with my things.
我们会检查的
We will check.
她看上去紧张兮兮的
She seems genuinely distressed.
我同意  他也似乎心神不宁
I agree. He seems unsettled.
要先顺着他们
Should just play along,
同情她
empathise with her.
她是个聪明的女孩
She is a clever girl.
看得出  她正在飞速思考
I can see her wheels turning.
我好奇  你怎么看马德里
I wonder, how you liked Madrid?
马德里  我不太明白
Madrid? I don't understand.
我们把你弄得很紧张吗
Are we making you nervous?
是的  我也看过些电影
Well, I mean, yeah. You know, I've seen these movies.
你知道的
You know,
美国人在国外因为莫须有的罪名
Americans thrown in jail in a foreign country
被关进监狱
for something they didn't do.
这俩孩子绝对不可能
There's no way these kids are responsible for
和五周前的那个案件有关联
what I saw five weeks ago.
不  我从没去过西班牙
No. I've never even been to Spain.
我们在罗马下的飞机
Look, we landed in Rome.
在那里待了一段时间
We spent a while there,
然后我们坐火车去巴黎  租了间小公寓
then we got a train to Paris and rented a little apartment.
有证据证明他们在巴黎吗
Do we have proof they were in Paris?
任何人都可以租一套公寓  但是不住里面
Anyone can rent an apartment and not stay in it.
他说得对
He's right.
你说什么  皮尔斯
What was that, Pierce?
他说  你说得对
He said you're right.
问她细节
Ask her about the details.
对
Yes.
问她细节  让她具体说
Ask her about the details. Make her be specific.
我们每天都在同一家餐馆吃饭
We ate at the same restaurant every day,
勒康普托餐厅
Le Comptoir.
如果你把包给我  我可以给你们看收据
If you get me my bag, I can show you the receipts.
就像我说的  我多少也是个收藏家
Like I said, I'm a bit of a collector.
好的  我们会检查的
Yeah, we'll have it checked.
她在撒谎
She is lying.
-或许在撒谎  -不
- Perhaps... - No.
她过于熟练了  肯定是排练过
She's too polished, it's rehearsed.
你得给她更多压力  给她设套
You've got to push her harder, trip her up.
让我进去
Let me in there.
卡农警探  拜托  办事要走流程
Detective Kanon, please, we have a process.
你们的流程有屁用
Your process sucks!
你离开巴黎之后去哪了
So where did you travel to from Paris?
卢森堡
Luxembourg,
本来觉得我不会喜欢那里  但我错了
which I did not expect to like, but we did.
展品  博物馆  还有圣母院
The exhibits, the museums, Notre-Dame...
当然  不是巴黎圣母院
Not the Notre-Dame,
但是  还是很美
but, beautiful.
有可能  或许就不是他俩
It is possible, I mean, maybe it is not them.
不  他们能骗得你们相信  上就是下
No. They would have you believing that up is down,
黑就是白
that black is white.
那个女孩
That girl...
That girl,
就是她杀了我的女儿
she killed my daughter.
我敢用我生命来赌
I will stake my life on it.
给我看看你参观过的博物馆的收据
Show me receipts from the museums you visited.
我真的很累了
I'm really tired.
请你找一下
Please, have a look.
好吧
Okay.
我特别喜欢博物馆
I love museums.
你看
See?
卢森堡的艺术论坛
Forum d'art in Luxembourg.
但我还是不明白
I still don't know how any of this
这些和命案有什么联系
is relevant to what happened.
我真的很想帮你们
Hey, I am really trying to be helpful here,
但我现在可以走了吗
but can we please go now?
再问一次
Once again,
你们到了伦敦  然后呢
you arrived to London. And then?
从伦敦又回到卢森堡
From London, back to Luxembourg,
然后去了捷克共和国
then Czech Republic,
现在我们就在这了
and now we're here.
你不管去哪都是用的现金
And everywhere you went, you paid with cash?
你得承认这并不怎么常见吧
You must admit that's not common.
你知道信用卡公司会收手续费吗
Do you know what credit card companies charge in fees?
这样才不会在旅游结束时
It's the only way to travel and not come back
回来欠一屁股债
to a mound of debt.
他们把所有答案都准备好了
A prepared answer for everything!
我们都在幼年时丧失双亲
Each of us lost our parents young
都只继承了一点遗产
and we both got a small inheritance.
孤独地在这世界上生存
Being alone in this world,
因此我们非常亲近
it's made us very, very close.
我们可以走了吗
Can we go now?
他们说的所有事都属实
Everything they say checks out.
西尔维娅和麦克·兰道夫
Sylvia and Mac Randolph,
分别是22岁  19岁
22 and 19,
住在洛杉矶
reside in Los Angeles.
他们证明了自己当时在
They have proof of being in places far away
距离命案地点很远的地方
from when and where the crimes took place.
他们可以在离开马德里的时候
They could've stopped in Paris
在巴黎停留
on their way from Madrid.
但我们没有证据
But we can't prove it.
找到证据前就把他们一直关着
Well, hold them until we can.
但为什么他们会去伦敦
But why would they go to London,
过海关是要护照的
where passports are required,
而且还住六点酒店
or book a hotel like the Six,
这不是故意让自己暴露在监视之下吗
if they're trying to stay under the radar?
他们只是装作好像没什么可隐藏的一样
To make it appear as if they've got nothing to hide.
他们行李中没有找到
Their luggage contains no match
和博物馆监控里相符合的衣物
for the clothes in the museum footage.
至少把他们留过夜
At least hold them overnight!
没有正式逮捕许可
I can't hold suspects more than 12 hours
我不能拘留嫌疑人超过12小时
without a formal arrest,
而且我也没有足够的证据去申请
which I can't make without sufficient evidence.
我们能做的就是命令他们
Best we can do is order them
以案件相关人的身份继续待在斯德哥尔摩
to remain in Stockholm as persons of interest,
标记他们的护照
mark their passports
一直监视他们
and keep them under surveillance.
你有见过那么薄的背景文件吗
I mean, have you ever seen a file so thin?
就好像直到4年前
It's like until four years ago,
他们都没存在过一样
they didn't exist.
国际刑警组织现正与美国协调合作
Interpol is coordinating with the US.
如果有什么线索的话  他们会查到的
If there is something out there, they'll find it.
听着
Listen,
我曾经办过一个案子
I had this case once.
一位著名建筑师的漂亮女儿
The beautiful daughter of the most celebrated architect
在德国  被殴打致死
in Germany, beaten to death.
她爸爸追查到了凶手
Her father hunted down the guy who did it
然后对他开了12枪
and shot him 12 times.
最后等事件平息下来后
Later, after the whole thing calmed down,
他开枪自杀了
he shot himself.
我不清楚你想让我怎么回答
I'm not real sure how you want me to respond to that.
正义得到伸张  并不代表结束
Getting justice won't be the end.
问题是每当我闭上眼时
You see, the problem is every time I close my eyes,
我看到的画面
the image that I see
就是我女儿躺在冰凉的停尸桌上
is my daughter laying on a cold slab.
这画面挥之不去
And that's never gonna go away.
我得走了
I have to go now.
一路平安
Safe travels.
等下
Wait.
想想她的微笑吧
Think of her smiling.
你怎么拿到的
How did you get this?
别问
Don't ask.
感觉就像我的脸在墙上
It is like I am bashing my face into a wall
撞了一次又一次
over and over again.
没事的
Hey, it's okay.
不  小丽
No, Val.
怎么可能没事  我告诉你
It's not okay. I am telling you,
所有人都有过去  所有人
everyone has a history. Everyone.
但这两个人  他们完全没有
But these two, there is just nothing.
他们就好像鬼魂一样
It's like they're goddamn ghosts.
要不我打个电话找人帮忙
Maybe I can call in a favour.
雅各布  你还在吗
Jacob? You still there?
在  我在
Yeah. Yeah, I'm here.
我在地检部门那边有些关系
I have some influence with the DA's office.
谢谢你能帮我  比尔
Thanks for doing this, Bill.
人们不停问我有什么可以帮忙的
People keep asking what they can do to help, and...
但真的没什么忙可帮  但我想
There really isn't anything. But I thought,
或许只有你能帮上
just maybe, you might.
你听过西蒙·海史密斯吗
Does the name Simon Haysmith mean anything to you?
你是说那个诈骗了几个
You mean the guy who defrauded some of
华尔街首富的男人
the richest men on Wall Street
诈骗金额达3亿美元
for, like, 300 million?
对  没错  就是他
Yeah, that's him. Yeah.
联邦政府花了一大笔纳税人的钱
The Feds spent a fortune in taxpayer dollars
准备起诉他
preparing to prosecute him.
但案件不怎么有利
They didn't have the case they wanted,
所以就从他的员工
so they squeezed his employees,
会计  律师下手
his accountants, attorneys...
但没有一个人吐露过一个字
But none of them said anything,
所以史上最大的白领罪犯
so one of the biggest white-collar criminals in history
就要逍遥法外了
was about to walk away.
他和金伯利有什么联系吗
What does this have to do with Kimberly?
当他们准备撤销指控时
Well, they were just about to drop the charges
莫名其妙地
when out of nowhere,
事情出现了转机
the case was just given to them.
他在布鲁塞尔  开曼群岛的
Bank account numbers in Brussels, Cayman Islands,
银行账号  等等一系列
and so on, and so on, and so on.
有人把他告发了
Somebody gave him up?
谁
Who?
他的儿子
His son.
那臭混蛋的儿子
The son of a bitch's son.
那孩子恨死他了  想毁了他
Kid detests him, wants him destroyed.
你是说麦克是海史密斯的儿子吗
Are you telling me that Mac is Haysmith's son?
是的
Yes, I am.
你知道他为什么要告发他父亲吗
Do you have any idea why he gave him up?
不知道
No,
我所能接触的范围内无从得知
not from the little bit I've been able to access.
事情的原委就藏在那一大堆
The real story is behind a shit-load of
加密文件里
redactions in that file.
证人保护计划
Witness protection.
他那时候还没成年吗
Was he a minor at the time?
是的
Yup.
这就是为什么局里
That's why the Bureau
对这整件事都守口如瓶
has kept tight-lipped about everything.
他那时候多大
And how old was he then?
-15岁  -他妻子呢
- Fifteen. - And the wife?
没有提到过
No mention.
那现在海史密斯在哪
And where's Haysmith?
在奥斯本服终身监禁
Doing life at Osborn.
你有办法去见他吗
Well, can you get in to see him?
我在想办法
Oh, I'm trying.
你没睡过觉吧
Did you sleep at all?
当你看着某人的眼睛时
You know when you look in someone's eyes
你就能看出他是不是在撒谎
and you know they're lying to you?
他们是有罪的
They're guilty.
在过去30年里我从来没有这么确定过
I've never been more sure about anything in 30 years.
他们发现了第五对夫妻
They've discovered a fifth couple.
阿姆斯特丹郊外
Outside Amsterdam.
一间画室  荒郊野岭的
Artist's studio, a bit away from everything.
目标记者已外出执行任务了
The targeted journalist was away on assignment.
暗示嫌疑人已被释放
你知道我要问什么
You know what I'm gonna ask.
至少现在你知道了
At least now you know.
是啊  至少我知道了
Yeah, at least I know.
她在收集它们
She collects them.
收据  她收集别人的收据
Receipts. She collects other people's receipts!
博物馆的  渡轮的  餐馆的
Museums, ferries, restaurants.
那些证明他们去过某地的实物证据
Physical proof of places they were supposed to have been!
艺术家必须要准备好牺牲所有
The artist must be prepared to sacrifice everything,
甚至自己的命
even life itself.
不允许软弱
No weakness!
"艺术乃化为光的伤"
"Art is a wound turned into light."
客房服务
Room service.
进来吧
Come in.
今晚过得好吗
How are we tonight?
很好  谢谢
Very well, thank you.
好  那边确认了
Okay, so they confirmed
他们是在酒店外订的客房服务
the room service order was placed from outside the hotel.
没想到这事居然这么普遍
Apparently it's more common than you'd think.
我得看一下详细的地图
I need to see a detailed map.
用我电脑吧  我得上厕所
Use my computer. I got to pee.
卡农警探
打扰一下  我找麦克和西尔维娅·兰道夫
Excuse me. Mac and Sylvia Randolph.
卡农警探  别进那房间
Detective Kanon, do not go to that room.
不  他们的不在场证明是编造的
No, they crafted their own alibi.
你们根本不知道面对的是什么角色
You have no idea what's staring you in the face.
你觉得他看到了吗
Do you think he saw?
不清楚
Not sure.
我们会处理好的
We'll take care of it.
警察  警察
Police! Police!
他们跑了
They're gone.
他们的护照都被标记了
We've marked their passports.
他们跑不远的
They can't go far.
他们没有什么地方去不了  好吗
They can go anywhere they damn well please.
雅各布
Jacob!
雅各布  我很抱歉
Jacob, I'm sorry.
我不知道你看了多少内容
I don't know how much you read,
但这不是什么小报曝光
but it's not just some tabloid expose.
这是关于你所失去的
It's about your loss
和你面对悲痛时的力量
and your strength in the face of it.
做你该做的吧
Do what you have to do.
我不会做任何事的
I don't have to do anything.
我不会上交稿子的
I'm not going to submit it.
他们跑了
They got away.
什么
What?
晚安  黛西
Good night, Dessie.
雅各布
Jacob.
我要睡了
I'm going to bed.
我不知道海史密斯会不会见我
I mean, who knows if Haysmith will agree to see me.
但我不能再坐家里无所事事了
I just can't sit at home doing nothing anymore.
瓦莱丽
Valerie...
这里可能锁了
It's probably locked.
是吗
Right?
还真是
Yes.
我是不是该试试后门
Okay, should I try the back?
非法闯入私人用地
You know, breaking and entering,
至少得判个10至15年
that is 10 to 15 minimum.
就这样吗
That's all?
这地方真大
Wow, this place is massive.
又一个空房间
Just another empty room.
等下  慢一点  那是什么
Wait, wait, wait, slow down. What is that?
我不知道但是这外面有个锁
I don't know but there's a lock on the outside.
很奇怪
It's weird.
有人吗  说你呢
Hello? Hello?
我已经叫警察了
I have called the police!
妈的  我等下再打给你
Oh, shit, I got to call you back.
我们这经常有擅自占用者
We're always having trouble with squatters,
谁让这房子空了快4年了呢
what with the house being empty for nearly four years.
不是占用者  就是媒体
And if it's not them, it's the press...
因为这里发生过的事
You know, what with what happened here.
你会原谅我吧  请你原谅我
Will you forgive me? Please forgive me.
-当然了  -我给你泡杯咖啡吧
- Of course. - Let me make you a coffee.
你真是太客气了  谢谢
Oh, you're so sweet, thank you.
我是你的新邻居  南希
I'm your new neighbour, Nancy.
我是瓦莱丽  很高兴认识你
Oh, Valerie. So nice to meet you.
顺便一说  我没有真报警
I didn't really call the police, by the way.
谢天谢地
Thank God.
那个叫小西蒙的男孩是我儿子埃文的朋友
The boy, Simon Jr, was friends with my son, Evan.
他是个好孩子  很聪明  体育很好
He was a sweet child. Very smart, good at sports.
他有时会来这里做作业
He came over here sometimes, to do his homework.
然后发生了一些变故  大概在
And then something changed, around...
我也记不清了
I don't remember exactly,
大概在他10岁的时候
maybe when he was 10?
什么变故
What changed?
他突然变得沉默寡言了
He kind of went quiet.
我知道有些地方不太对劲  但说不通
I knew something was wrong, but it didn't make any sense.
-至少那时候说不通  -什么意思
- Not then, at least. - What do you mean?
老西蒙和我丈夫一样
Well, Simon Sr was on two boards with my husband,
也是一个大慈善家  和教会积极成员
a big philanthropist and an active member of the church.
他妻子伊琳娜  是一位全职妈妈
His wife, Irina, was a stay-at-home mom.
她太美了
Oh, she was beautiful.
她长得有点像梅拉尼娅·特朗普
She looked a bit like Melania Trump,
第45任美国总统唐纳德·特朗普的第三任妻子
有一双斯拉夫式的大眼睛
with those big Slavic eyes.
我觉得她以前是个模特  从俄罗斯来的
She used to be a model, I think, from Russia originally.
再加点酒吗
Mmm, more wine?
我不该再喝了
Oh, I shouldn't.
如果你想听完整个故事  就必须得再喝点
If you want the whole story, you most definitely should.
谢谢你
Thank you.
她以前可喜欢烤馅饼了
She loved to bake pies.
在感恩节前后  她会烤五种不同的馅饼
Around Thanksgiving, she would bake five different kinds.
他们俩看起来就是天生一对
They seemed to be the perfect couple.
然后她就自杀了
And then she killed herself.
天呐  怎么自杀的
Oh, my God. How?
上吊的  孩子们找到的她
Hanging. The kids found her.
"孩子们"  西蒙还有
Oh, "kids." Simon...
西蒙还有个姐姐  玛丽娜
Simon had an older sister, Marina.
他们的父亲太严厉了
Their father was so strict,
孩子们总是说
the kids were always,
"好的  谢谢"还有"谢谢您  夫人"
"Yes, please" and "Thank you, ma'am."
他迫使他们在各方面都做到最好
He pushed them to be the best at everything,
总是拖着他们去看艺术展或者听讲座
forever dragging them to some art exhibition or lecture.
一点娱乐活动都不想让他们有
Didn't seem to want them to have any fun.
从来不过任何节日
Never, ever went on holidays.
有一次  玛丽娜把冰激凌滴到衣服上了
One time, Marina dripped ice cream on her top.
老西蒙把她带进屋里
And Simon Sr took her inside the house.
他们出来之后  她就闭口不言了
And when they came out, she wouldn't speak,
一个字都不肯说
wouldn't say a word.
你知道发生什么了吗
Did you find out what happened?
我后来才知道  他打得特别狠
I found out later, he had beaten her so hard,
她背上都是鞭痕
she had welts on her backside.
我的邻居很残忍
My neighbour was cruel...
他要求他的家庭尽善尽美
He demanded perfection from his family,
尤其是他的孩子们
especially his children,
一旦他们没有达到他的高要求
and if they didn't achieve his high standards immediately,
他就会用鞭子抽他们
he would whip it out of them.
我把我的疑虑告诉过我丈夫
I told my husband I had suspicions,
但他让我别管闲事
but he just told me to mind my own business.
你知道他们现在在哪吗
Do you know where they are now?
自从玛丽娜离家去上寄宿学校就没见过了
Haven't seen Marina since she left for boarding school,
我觉得西蒙被儿童保护组织接走了
and I think Simon was taken by Child Protective Services.
比利时\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h布鲁塞尔
这不符合以往作案模式
It's a break in the pattern.
他们不是夫妻  谋杀案之间间隔更短
Not a married couple, fewer days between murders,
也没有明显暴力痕迹
and no real signs of violence.
其实梅利兹先生和里尼克先生刚刚结婚
Actually, Mr Melitz and Mr Riniker were recently married.
比利时是最早允许
Belgium was one of the first countries
同性婚姻的国家之一
to allow same-sex marriage.
这就是案发地
This is where it happened.
请问能给我一下明信片吗
我们在有线新闻网办公室里发现了这张明信片
We found this postcard at the CNN offices.
等等  还有照片吗
Wait, was there a photograph with it?
没有照片
No photo.
又回到了原点
汉斯·杜邦
比利时\h\h布鲁塞尔
莱西讷街200号
"又回到了原点"
"It has come full circle."
字迹不太一样
The handwriting looks different.
没有照片  没有截掉的肢体部位
No photograph. No unconnected body parts.
同性伴侣
Gay couple...
你觉得是模仿作案吗
You think it's a copycat?
兰道夫夫妇是怎么离开斯德哥尔摩
How could the Randolphs have
却没被侦察到的
left Stockholm undetected?
看
Look.
布格罗的《地狱中的但丁和维吉尔》
Bouguereau's Dante and Virgil in Hell.
比尔让我去见海史密斯  我得走了
Bill's got me in to see Haysmith. I got to run.
瓦莱丽
Valerie...
好  好  我会小心的
Yes, yes, I'll be careful.
布布利兹把照片发来了
Bublitz sent the photos, and also
还发来了阿姆斯特丹罪案现场的照片
the crime scene photos of Amsterdam.
看
Look.
等一下  倒回去
Wait, wait, go... Go back.
那是我外婆的戒指
That's my grandmother's ring.
那是我女儿的手
That's my daughter's hand!
我很抱歉
I'm so sorry.
那是我女儿的手
That's my daughter's hand.
不
No.
抱歉
I'm sorry.
我女儿的手
My daughter's hand...
你有15分钟时间  夫人
Got 15 minutes, ma'am.
抱歉一直盯着你看
Forgive me for staring.
你是我这么久以来
You're the first good-looking woman
见到的第一个漂亮女人
I've seen in a very long time.
你的头脑配得上这张脸蛋吗
Do you have a mind to match that face?
头脑聪慧到能让我出去吗
A mind brilliant enough to get me out of here?
我们正在准备立案上诉
We're building a case to launch an appeal.
我在你儿子提供的证据中
I found a number of inconsistencies
发现了一些矛盾之处
in the evidence provided by your son.
他们告诉你他毁了一幅德·库宁的画吗
Did they tell you he defiled a de Kooning?
他们俩曾经拥有一切  一切
Those two had everything. Everything!
他们所受的教育是钱买不来的
You cannot buy the kind of education they had.
尊重金钱对你很重要  是吗
Respect for money is important to you, isn't it?
当然
Of course.
仔细听我说
Listen to me very carefully.
此非父之罪
The sins of the father this is not.
能解释一下吗
Care to elaborate?
卡农女士  我们只有15分钟时间
We have 15 minutes together, Ms Kanon,
我们能别把时间都浪费在
can we please not spend it talking about
这些忘恩负义的混蛋上吗
these ungrateful bastards?
我们谈谈政治  谈谈艺术吧
Let's talk about politics, art.
我们来谈谈立体派的晚期作品
Let's talk about the late works of the Cubists,
为何表现主义是对法西斯主义的反应
how the Expressionists were a reaction to fascism.
或者被送去寄宿学校对你的孩子有什么影响
Or how being sent to boarding school affects your child?
你女儿怎么了
What happened to your daughter?
好像没有她的消息
There seems no trace of her.
我们在找原因
We're looking for cause.
小西蒙为什么要编造你的故事
Why would Simon Jr make up stories about you?
你知道在这里你的感官会变得更敏锐吗
Did you know your senses get heightened in this place?
我也不知道为什么
I don't know why.
可能是因为噪音
Perhaps it's all the noise,
随后便是寂静
followed by the silence.
父亲的职责在于教育  我做到了
A father's duty is to teach, and I did just that.
我教授他们文化  伦理  道德  规矩
I taught them culture, ethics, morality, discipline.
是吗
Is that right?
你和她一样
Oh, you're just like her.
狡猾的小贱人
Devious little bitch.
年轻女孩只要做到一件事
Young girls need to be just that.
做年轻女孩就好
Young girls.
你会一起找到他们
You'll find them together.
无法把他们分开
You can't keep them apart...
除非强迫他们
Except by force.
这你可是最拿手的
That's something you're very good at.
你在对我评头论足[审判]吗
Oh, are you judging me?
我觉得法庭已经这么做了
Oh, I think a court already did that.
社会上到处都是正派的人做出的错误选择
Well, society is full of wrong decisions made by decent people.
就拿我来说吧
Take me, for example.
我见了你
I met with you
因为我还以为你能帮我
because I actually thought you might be able to help me.
你的判断真是大错特错
Well, that was a huge error of judgement on your part.
我想你应该不会处理我的上诉吧
So I take it you won't be handling my appeal.
幸会了  夫人
Enchante, madame.
幸会
Enchante.
看来海史密斯的怒火
It seems the majority of Haysmith's rage was...
主要集中在女孩身上
Was focused on the girl.
玛丽娜被送去寄宿学校
So, Marina gets sent away to boarding school,
西蒙不惜一切也要把她接回来
and Simon stops at nothing to get her back.
这可真是个亲弟弟
That is one hell of a brother.
除非
Unless...
除非背后还有隐情
Unless it's more than that.
什么意思
What do you mean?
瓦莱丽说海史密斯管玛丽娜叫
Valerie said that Haysmith
"狡猾的小贱人"
called Marina "a devious bitch",
但他还说了什么
but he also said something about
年轻女孩只要做年轻女孩就好
young girls needing to be young girls,
得要强迫他们才能把他们分开
and that it would take force to keep them apart.
天呐
Christ.
麦克和西尔维娅·兰道夫
Mac and Sylvia Randolph...
他们就是玛丽娜和西蒙·海史密斯
They are Marina and Simon Haysmith.
什么
What?
我是说我们追遍整个欧洲的嫌犯
I mean, our suspects that we've been chasing across Europe,
他们没有结婚  不是
they're not married, they're not...
他们不是夫妻
They're not husband and wife,
他们是姐弟
they are brother and sister.
《施洗者圣约翰》的头
Head of Saint John the Baptist.
什么
What?
《施洗者圣约翰》的头
Head of Saint John the Baptist.
对那个虐待狂混蛋的最佳致敬
A fitting tribute to that sadistic bastard.
我们得确保所有人都知道
We have to make sure that everyone knows,
最重要的是说出原因
and most importantly, why.
他把美好的东西变得残酷又丑陋
He took beauty and made it cruel and ugly.
你觉得他们会让他看到吗
Will they even let him see, do you think?
我想让他看到毁灭  玛丽娜
I want him to see the destruction, Marina.
我想让他受伤
I want him to hurt
像我们一样
like we did.
我在这
I'm here.
我就在这
I'm right here.
我们已经颠覆了他对完美的观念
We have fucked with his notion of perfection.
这比监禁更能深入他的脑海
That'll get inside his mind like no incarceration can.
我知道不该这么想  但我总觉得
I know I shouldn't, but I almost feel...
他们在讲自己的故事
They're playing out their story.
听着  《吻》代表恋人被迫分离的痛苦
Look, The Kiss, the pain of lovers torn apart.
《农神吞噬其子》
Saturn Devouring His Son,
代表毁了他们一生的父亲
the father that destroyed their lives.
这一切都有可怕扭曲的意义
It all makes horrible, twisted sense.
爱情  痛苦  死亡
Love, pain, death...
了结
Completion.
是啊  但最后一张明信片还有个省略号
Yeah, but the last postcard still had an ellipsis.
他们还没结束
They're not finished yet.
他们想传达  他们的爱是合理的
The message they're sending is that their love is valid.
他们对世界不接受他们而感到愤怒
They are angry at the world for not accepting them.
我觉得布鲁塞尔的谋杀案是精准
I think the murders in Brussels were exact
并带有目的性的  不是随机的
and purposeful, not random.
为什么
Why?
因为上百年来禁忌的爱情
Because other forms of love, for centuries forbidden,
现在已经被大多数人所接受了
are now accepted by most,
但他们的没有
but not theirs.
在无能为力时仍能保持强大
To feel powerful in the face of powerlessness.
是的  没错
Yeah, exactly.
如果我们把那个夺走呢
What if we took that away from them?
什么意思
How do you mean?
你要写的那篇关于我的文章
That article you were going to write about me...
我叫戴夫·本宁斯  我和我的兄弟们一起
My name is Dave Bennings and I'm with my brothers,
布莱恩和杰西  以及我的搭档彼得
Brian and Jesse, and our partner, Peter.
西蒙  宝贝  过来
Simon, babe, come here.
"在过去两周里
"Over the last two weeks,
我目睹了一场连环杀人案的调查
I've had a front-row seat to the investigation
这起案件被称为'明信片杀戮'
of the serial murders dubbed 'The Postcard Killings'.
此案占据了新闻头条
"They've dominated our headlines,
但媒体的分析是错的
"but the media analysis is wrong.
虽然听起来很反常
"As odd as it sounds,
但是这些罪行并非被嗜血或残忍所驱使
"these crimes are not driven by bloodlust or cruelty.
他们反而是在渴求一份理解
"Instead, they are a cry for understanding..."
我跟着雅各布·卡农警探在前线跟踪此案
"I've had a front-row seat via Detective Jacob Kanon,
他是其中一名美籍受害人的父亲
"the American father of one of the victims.
他和我一样  在这里都是外人
"He's an outsider here, like me,
但是他绝不会让这世界的残酷
"but he will not let the grimness of this world
阻碍他为自己的女儿
"distract him from his commitment
伸张正义
"to find justice for his daughter.
因为与凶手的家庭不同
"Because unlike the killers' family,
这位父亲的爱是全心全意的
"this father's love is 100%..."
从罪案之凶残明显可以看出
"It is obvious from the brutality of the crimes
凶手在童年受到过非人的虐待
"that the killers had a horribly abusive childhood.
他们一直谨遵写在明信片上的文字
"The words on their postcards have been kept guarded,
但他们也展现出了
"but they reveal a rage
对于自己所做奋斗的正当性
"and passionate commitment to the validity
所持有的怒火与狂热的执着
"of their own struggle...
而那奋斗正是他们传达的信息
"And that struggle is their message.
信息的内容即为正义
"And that message is justice..."
但现在我们听见了你们的声音  请住手
"But now we have heard you, and you can stop.
这对我而言很难受  也很可怕
"This has been difficult for me, and frightening,
但是雅各布让我看见
"but Jacob has shown me
何谓真正的优秀
"what it means to be really good.
优秀的警探
"A good detective,
优秀的父亲
"a good father,
优秀的人"
"a good man."
我们就用她作我们的收官之作
We make her our final piece.
有了她  一切就都完整了
She makes everything complete.
或许我们该住手了
Maybe we should stop.
搞辆车  就此消失
Get a car, disappear.
不行
No.
或许我们应该分开
Maybe we should split up?
我们不能分开
We're not splitting up!
我只想过正常的生活
I want to live a normal life.
这就是我们的目标  争取正常生活的机会
That's what we are doing, creating a chance for that.
艺术家一生都不受人待见
Artists were judged in their lifetimes,
我们也一样
just as we are.
我天  你真的在意这个吗
My God, do you really care about this?
我在意的只有失去你
All I care about is losing you.
我发过誓会保护你
我说到做到
我很害怕
我们不该再躲躲藏藏了
We shouldn't have to hide anymore.
我去找警察
I went to the police
就是为了我们不用再这样生活
so that we didn't have to live like this.
他没法再伤害你了
坚强点
我们就快到家了
未知联系人
"隆巴德女士  谢谢
"Thank you, Ms Lombard,
谢谢你用应有的尊重讲出了我们的故事
"for telling our story with the meaningful heart it deserves.
大幕已经拉开"
"The curtain is pulled back."
我没懂
I don't understand.
铁幕  他们母亲是俄罗斯人
Iron Curtain. Mother was Russian.
将苏联和东欧共产党国家与西欧分开的边界
伊琳娜·斯米尔诺娃  她在圣彼得堡出生
Irina Smirnova, she, erm, was born in St Petersburg.
苏联解体之后
She moved to the US with her parents
她跟随父母搬去美国
after the Soviet Union collapsed.
我猜测他们现在
My guess is they're travelling
又在用西蒙和玛丽娜·海史密斯的名字出行
under the name Simon and Marina Haysmith again,
用的是俄罗斯的护照
using their Russian passports.
这也解释了他们是如何离开瑞典
Which would explain how they left Sweden.
以及如何跨越国界的
And how they passed across borders.
如果我们查一下
If we checked,
我赌海史密斯在用布鲁塞尔的银行账户
I'll bet Haysmith is using a bank account in Brussels.
又说不定布鲁塞尔不是要甩掉我们
Or what if Brussels was not to throw us off,
只是想迷惑我们
just to redirect our thinking.
不  我们知道他们在往东北方走
No, look, we know that they're heading northeast.
他们只要穿过赫尔辛基另一边的国界
They cross the border on the other side of Helsinki,
斯德哥尔摩-赫尔辛基-圣彼得堡
就离圣彼得堡很近了
they're damn near in St Petersburg.
只要他们进了俄罗斯  就基本抓不到了
If they make it to Russia, they're virtually untouchable.
没有引渡条约
No extradition treaties.
天啊  我们怎么这么背
Jesus. Why can't we catch a break here?
今早巴黎的一家报社收到一张明信片
A postcard turned up at a newspaper in Paris this morning,
还有汉堡  布达佩斯
and in Hamburg, and in Budapest...
写了什么
What did they say?
都是同一句话
All the same.
"如今我们已重生"
"Now we are reborn."
以省略号结尾吗
With a "dot, dot, dot"?
不  就是句号
No, just a single dot.
我会通知霍格伦德和国际刑警
I'll loop in Hoglund and Interpol,
看看我们能不能追踪电子邮件
see if we can trace the email.
欧洲各地都在进行搜捕
There's a manhunt across Europe.
同时你别轻举妄动  朋友
In the meantime sit tight, my friend.
那是绝不可能了
Not a chance in hell.
我要回慕尼黑了
I'm going back to Munich.
我懂
Understood.
你做分内的事
You do what is expected.
我做该做的事
I'm going to do what's needed.
我知道你很清楚怎么开枪
I know you know how to use this.
你有你能决定该不该用这枪
Only you can determine if you should.
罗马有人在电视上认出他们了
寄给那记者的邮件有什么进展
我们查到一个IP地址
登录历史追溯到在罗马一家店注册的账号
同时购买的还有一台新平板电脑
定位呢
我们正在追踪
芬兰\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h赫尔辛基
这里离俄罗斯边境有多远
How far to the Russian border?
三小时左右  这是唯一的路
Around three hours. There's only one road.
取车处
西蒙  是他们
该回家了
我刚回来  在邮箱里看到这个
连邮票都没有
为明信片杀手辩护
-是他们吗  -对  就是他们
- Is it them? - Yeah, it's them.
黛西
Dessie!
早安
Morning.
我们就知道你会明白
We knew you'd figure it out.
是麦克想到要提大幕拉开
It was Mac's idea to mention the curtain being pulled back.
我们的母亲是我们一生中唯一的美好
Our mother was the one good thing in our lives.
她在努力让我们不受他的伤害
She tried to protect us from him.
但怪物始终是怪物
But monsters will remain monsters,
无论你用什么办法去驯化它们
no matter what you try to do to tame them.
数个世纪以来  艺术家勾勒出无数杀戮的瞬间
For centuries, artists have killed things in a moment.
我们重塑了他们的杰作
We reinvented that.
你写到我们怒气的程度时
When you wrote about the intensity of our rage,
如此一针见血
it was so perceptive.
你们很幸运能拥有彼此
You were lucky to have each other.
我父亲也不是什么好人
My father wasn't a good man either.
要是我有个弟弟  或许也会好过一点
If I'd had a brother, it would have been easier.
那个男人只配烂在阴曹地府
That man deserves to rot in hell.
谁能说我们的感受就"无法接受"
Who can say how we feel is "unacceptable"?
爱就是爱
Love is love.
我喜欢你
I like you.
那你为什么不放我走
So why don't you let me go?
停车  停车
Hey, stop, stop!
-我不会  -麦克  这里就好
- I wouldn't... - Mac, this is good.
麦克  停车
Mac, stop the car.
听我说
Listen...
西尔维娅  求你了  放我走
Sylvia, listen, please... Let me go!
求你了
Please.
我好冷
I'm so cold...
很快就结束了
It won't take very long.
我保证  你不会感到一丝疼痛
And I promise, you won't feel any pain.
好吗
Okay?
我们可以开始了吗
We good to go?
非常好
Perfect.
他们在那里
There they are.
莫迪利亚尼的《斜躺的裸女》
Modigilani's Reclining Nude.
"艺术乃化为光的伤"
"Art is a wound turned into light."
你把这个喝了  就感觉不到疼了  好吗
Look, you drink this, you won't feel any pain. Okay?
-喝吧  -快点
- Come on. - Come on.
-天啊  -去你的
- Christ! - Fuck you!
你真觉得你能阻止这事吗
Do you think that you can stop this?
再来一次
Now, one more time.
离她远点
Step away from her.
手伸到我能看见的地方
Hands where I can see them.
你女儿很可爱
Your daughter was lovely.
闭嘴
Shut up.
她手指很修长  很优雅
She had the longest fingers, so graceful.
你根本不认识我女儿
You didn't know my daughter.
你没资格提她
You don't get to talk about her.
但她说起过你
But she talked about you.
她说了你的很多事
She talked about you a lot.
她说很希望孩子对父母离婚也有发言权
She said she wished kids had a say in their parents' divorce.
我们的父亲跟你完全不同
Our father was nothing like you.
但你们的母亲
But your mother...
她过世的时候  你们一定很伤心吧
It must have really hurt when she died, huh?
他夺走了她的一切
He took everything from her,
直到她一无所有
till there was nothing left.
玛丽娜  你还好吗
Marina, we okay?
不要
No!
不  不
No! No!
你不去追他们吗
You're not gonna go after them?
他们哪里都去不了
Nowhere for them to go.
玛丽娜  我们是在回家吗
Marina, are we going home?
对  那里永不日落  永远不会
Yes. The sun never sets there. Never.
那里的人会接受我们
We'll be accepted.
再也没人能伤害我们
No one can hurt us again.
你好啊
Hello.
你好
Hey.
我还担心再也见不到你了
I was worried I wasn't gonna get to see you again.
准备好出院了吗
Ready to go?
-准备好了  -我来拿那个
- Yes, I am. - Let me carry that.
你们国家的人会在吃早饭的时候
Your countrymen will be reading the salacious details
读到这些反胃的细节
over their cornflakes.
不知怎么的  好像加重了整个悲剧
Somehow just compounds the tragedy of it all.
海史密斯手上沾满了鲜血
Haysmith has enormous amounts of blood on his hands.
而且真的
And really,
完全没跟家人联系吗
no family connection at all?
他们一出生就被领养了
They were adopted at birth
相隔三年  从两个州领养的
three years apart, from two different states.
根据新闻报道
According to press reports,
他预付了这个律师
he had this attorney on retainer.
他很清楚自己要什么
Was very specific on what he wanted.
-麻烦签名  -长相  背景
- Sign, please. - Looks, background...
早期最好的基因工程
Early genetic engineering at its finest.
一点没错
Exactly.
感觉他不只是情感感知无能
Seemingly, he was impotent in more than just the emotional sense.
该死  你要知道
Damn, you know...
西蒙和玛丽娜本来可以结婚的
Simon and Marina, they could have gotten married,
从此幸福生活在一起
lived happily ever after,
而我女儿和其他那些人
and my daughter and all those others...
他们就都还能活着
They would still be alive.
一切都安排好了  去机场的车
Everything is arranged, car to the airport,
有飞机送你去伦敦  这样你就能
a plane to take you to London so that you...
你也知道
Well, you know,
带她回家
bring her home.
是啊
Yeah.
你是个好人
You're a good man.
谢谢你做的一切
Thank you for everything.
等找到他们的尸体了  你要告诉我
And you'll let me know when they find their bodies?
能跟你合办我的最后一案真好
It was nice to have you with me on my last case.
你明天会干什么
What will you do tomorrow?
把帮我遛狗的姑娘炒了
Fire my dog walker.
别最后跟我一样
Don't end up like me.
找一个新的开始
Find a new beginning.
我们养育了一个了不起的孩子
We raised a great kid.
她生前很快乐
She was happy.
至少我们还是做对了一些事
Well, at least we got something right.
我觉得我们做得都很好
I think we got it all right.
直到事情变了
Till we didn't.
"我们"吗
"We"?
可能你不太想  但是
You probably don't want to, but,
大家都要回我家
people are coming back to my place...
我一会儿就过去找你
Oh... I will see you there in a bit.
丫头
Oh, kiddo.
我会非常想念你的
I'm gonna miss you so much.
喂
Yeah?
海史密斯
Haysmith.
干嘛
Yeah.
有你电话
You got a call.
谢谢
Thanks.
喂  你好
Hello? Hello?
喂
Hello?
你好  父亲
是我
明信片杀戮